Guide to the International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences Records 1970-1984
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence, Papers and Registration Materials
  - Various correspondence, K, replacement file, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Various correspondence, L, replacement file, order forms, 1975-1976 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - M, Order forms, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Roberta McGowan, boxed paper orders filled by Monarch printing corp., 1973 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - N-O, order forms, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - P-Q, order forms, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Paper order, undated (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Pope, P., paper orders, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Pope, P., paper orders, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Pope, P., paper orders, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Pope, P., paper orders, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - R, orders for reprints, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - S, orders for reprints, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - T, orders for reprints, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - W, orders for reprints, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - U-V, orders for reprints, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - X, Y, Z, orders for reprints, 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Orders for reprints, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Letter explaining the general catalog, undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Orders not yet completed, undated (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Orders for reprints, requests for catalogues, letters from those who never received papers, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Papers in stock, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Reproduction of conference papers, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Special paper orders, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Paper orders, (queries), 1973-1975 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Series III: Materials for Conference Packets
  - Materials for conference packets, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Conference packet mock up, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Chicago guide, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Conference binder, blue, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Conference binder, green, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Congress brochures, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Congress logo and picture symbols from ICAES, final program, printers originals, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Information for participant packets, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Printer’s originals for packets, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - ISR Newsletter, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - List of Papers, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - List of Papers, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Maps and graphic presentations, undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Map packet, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Plan of the congress, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Program lists for the conference, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Program, final draft for packet, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Special events, preliminary information, IXTH INT’L Congress, 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Union and Congress, introduction, 1971-3 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Xeroxes from conference organizations, preliminary information, 1971-1982 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Xeroxes from conference organizations, preliminary information, 1971-1982 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Xeroxes from conference organizations, preliminary information, 1971-1982 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Xeroxes from conference organizations, preliminary information, 1971-1982 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Xeroxes from conference organizations, preliminary information, 1971-1982 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Xeroxes from conference organizations, preliminary information, 1971-1982 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Xeroxes from conference organizations, preliminary information, 1971-1982 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Series IV: Research on other Conferences and Institutions
  - AAA Annual Management, NY, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Casiana, Gaceta Gazette Las Casian, organizing for the 500th year celebration of birth of de Las Casas includes correspondence with Gertrude Bloom, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Chicago metro project, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Chicago metro project, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - C.I.P.S.H. d’Ormesson, 1967-1976 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Commission on Ethnocide and Genocide, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Museum and Relations to ICOM/ Gessian, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - The Court of Man, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Ethnic Groups, Illinois consultation on ethnicity in education, history of Chicago, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Georgia Mobile Lab, proceedings, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Indigena, contribution form, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - International Union Congress, Kraeder, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Israel conference, 1982-1984 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Live conferences, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Local interests, Chicago Public Library, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Local interest, Field Museum, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Local interest, University of Chicago, Quad. Club, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Local interest, urbanologist, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Mobilization of Anthropological Knowledge, IUAES 1977 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Osh Kosh conference, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Program Center for Continuing education, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Smithsonian conferences, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Unisist, undated (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Urgent Anthropology Commission, 1973, 1 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Delegation and Advisory Council, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - World Population, Commission on Population, United Nation, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Series V: Materials for Cultural Programs
  - American Folk Concert, reviews and news clippings, tickets, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - American Folk Concert Records from Smithsonian, restricted financial material?, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - American Folk Concert, Lomax, Alan, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Archaeology, Illinois archaeology tours, 1973, Book fair, arts and crafts fair, publisher’s exhibits, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Book fair, arts and crafts fair, publisher’s exhibits, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Book fair, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Commemorative Stamp, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - ICAES Denim Bag, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Exhibits, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Exhibits, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Exhibits, Food, Science and Technology, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Film Festival, Chicago Children's Choir, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Society of Eastern Arts, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Special events, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Special events, archaeology tour, mobile exhibit, museum visits, art exhibits, undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Special events, children's choir, Tamu Tamu, archaeology tour, American folk concert, see oversize, undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Tamu Tamu, Gian Carlo Menotti, Letters, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Tamu Tamu, 1973-1974 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Tamu Tamu, Gian Carlo Menotti, correspondence and reviews, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Tamu Tamu, Gian Carlo Menotti, letter, review, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Tamu Tamu, NY Times, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Tamu Tami. News clippings, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Tamu Tamu, opera photographs, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Tamu Tamu, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Tamu Tamu, reviews, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Youth for Mankind Conference
  - Budget, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Conference, actual schedules, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, responses, bills, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Children's International Summer Villages, requests and responses, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Children's International Summer Villages, information and lists, 1968-1972 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, unfiled, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, never filed, summer conference planner, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to Sol Tax, unanswered, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - CPC, relations with high schools, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - De Paul University, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Embassies, correspondence, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Embassies, carbons of embassy addresses, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Embassies, Letters to China and Russia, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Embassies, correspondence, A-B, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Embassies, correspondence, C-D, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Embassies, correspondence, E-F, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Embassies, correspondence, G-H, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Embassies, correspondence, I, J, K, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Embassies, correspondence, L-M, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Embassies, correspondence, N-P, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Embassies, correspondence, R-S, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Embassies, correspondence, T-Z, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Embassies, US Embassy, no response, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - French translation, information sheet, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Fund raising efforts, foundation cover letters, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Fund raising efforts, foundation answers, (mostly declining to fund YFM), 1973 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Fund raising efforts, independent source donations, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Fund raising efforts, Material donations, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Fund raising efforts, funding sources, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - HS youth, conference meeting, committee and student interest slips, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Members, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Organization, undated (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Packets and form letters, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Conference packet, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Participants, definite, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Letter to definite participants, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Peripheral organizations, contacted, brochures, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Peripheral organizations, contacted, brochures, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Planning Bulletins, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Planning Bulletins, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Planning Committee, Chicago, people lists, undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Planning Committee, bulletins, undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Planning, facilities, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Post conference, publicity, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Post conference correspondence, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Public relations and advertising, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Research grant application, program, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Resume and information sheets, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Resume, draft (handwritten), 1973 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Resume and information sheets, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Resume, drafts, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Resume, 4th draft, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Resume, evolution of drafts and final product, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - School directories for Illinois and Chicago, 1971-1972 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Stationary, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Tax, Sol, instigating preparations for the YFM conference), 1972 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Various, seminar plans, calendar, facilities, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Series VII: Photographs and Publicity for ICAES
  - Photographs of Sol Tax, Ronald Swartz, J. Cordwell, Sam Stanley, K. Red Corn and Perry Ialor, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Youth for Mankind, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Chronicle, news clippings, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - News clippings, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, unidentified participants, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Man of Mankind, news clipping, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Media, Radio, Television, Literature, advanced interest, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Media during congress, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Press release, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - News clippings, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - News clippings, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - News clippings, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - The Times Literary Supplement, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Publication Materials
  - Subseries 1: General Publication Materials
    - Book editor outline, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Brochures, World Anthropology volume list, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Central paragraphs to general editor's preface, undated (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - CK's index, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Comité de patronage, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Copy editing, (Mer), 1973 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Copyright information, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Druke, Mary, status of individual papers for publication, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Editors, 1873 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Editors, 1873 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Things to tell and ask editors, 1972-1973 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Forward, preface and introduction, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Indexing of book, 1974-1975 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Lists of editors, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - List, projected volumes, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Meeting to schedule World Anthropology production, 1975-1977 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Monthly sales reports from Mouton Publishers, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Mouton Publishers and Aldine Publishing, correspondence, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Mouton Publishers and Aldine Publishing, correspondence, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Mouton Publishers and Barnkamp, 1975-1977 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Mouton Publishers, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Mouton Publishers, Peter de Ridder, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Mouton Publishers, Peter de Ridder, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Mouton Publishers, Peter de Ridder, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Mouton Publishers and Mer, 1973-1974 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Mouton Publishers and Mer, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Notes on papers, orders, volumes and inventories, undated (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Potential editors, 1973-1973 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Royalty reports, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Secondary publication, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Various materials, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - U.S. distribution and promotion (Aldine), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Abstracts
    - Registration cards, abstracts, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Abstracts, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Abstracts, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Abstracts, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Abstracts, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Abstracts, Russian, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Abstracts, Volume, shipping, mailing, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 3: Editorial Correspondence and Corrections
    - Givens, R.D. and Martin Nettleship, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Givens, R.D. and Martin Nettleship, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Holloman, R., correspondence, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Holloman, R., correspondence, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Holloman, R., and Leo Depres, correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Holloman, R., and Leo Depres, correspondence, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Holloman, R., 1972 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Huizer, Gerrit and Brue Mannheim, correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - IUAES, correspondence with editors and publishers, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Mouton publishers, M. Maruyama, corrections and insults, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - M. Maruyama, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - McCormack, William correspondence with S.A. Wurm, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - McCormack, William correspondence with S.A. Wurm, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - McCormack, William correspondence with S.A. Wurm, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - McCormack, William correspondence with S.A. Wurm, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - McCormack, William correspondence with S.A. Wurm, 1975-1977 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Maddock, Kenneth, correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Mavalwala, J., correspondence, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Meier, Otten, senior editor, (part of ms is missing), post congress, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Charles Merbs and Giles, correspondence, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Merbs, Charles, correspondence, undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Nash, June and Jorge Dandler, correspondence, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Newell, William H., correspondence, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Osh Kosh, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Polgar, Steven, correspondence, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Pitt, David C., correspondence, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Preston, James, correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Quimby, George, correspondence, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Safa, Helen and Brian M. du Toit, correspondence, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Raphael, Dana, correspondence, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Raphael, Dana, correspondence, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Rapoport, Amos, correspondence, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Rapoport, Amos, correspondence, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Rohrlich,-Leavitt, Ruby, correspondence, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Reeds, Charles, correspondence, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Rohrlich, Leavitt, correspondence, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Rubin, Vera, correspondence, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Sliverberg, James, 1972-1978 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 4: Conference Papers and Original Drafts
    - A-AL, Abromova, Z.A., conference papers, 1973 Abdushelishvily, M.B., conference papers, 1973 Abramson, S.M, conference papers, 1973 Adams, John W. and Alice B. Kasakoff, conference paper, 1973 Adams, Robert McC., conference paper, 1973 Afendreas, Evangelos A., conference paper, 1973 Agajanov S.G. and A. Kavryev, conference paper, 1973 Ahmed, Nizam Uddin, conference papers, 1973 Alekseeva, T.I., conference paper, 1973 Alexeenko, E.A., conference paper, 1973 Al Faruqi, L.I., conference paper, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - AM-AZ, Amos, Ajato, draft, 1973 Andersen, Raoul, draft, 1974 Andreev, I.L., conference paper, 1973 Andreev, I.L., conference paper, 1973 Andrianove, B.V. and N.N. Cheboxaron, conference paper, 1973 Araki, Hiroyuki, draft, 1973 Arens, William, reprint, undated Armstrong, Robert G., conference paper, 1973 Aschenbrenner, Joyce and Lloyd Collins, undated Arutyunyan, Yu. V., conference paper, 1973 Atallah, Borham, conference paper, 1973 Atherton, John H., conference paper, 1973 Atkinson, M. Jourdan, conference paper and draft, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Abdel-Hameed, F. draft, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Abu-Laban, Baha, draft. 1973 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Aignor, J.S. draft, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Bettie Scott, draft, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Albert, Stuart, draft, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Anonymous, "Background of Comedy," draft, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Anonymous, "Ethnology, Modern Problems in the USSR," bibliography, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Anonymous, "Identity and Opposition," draft, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Anonymous, untitled draft, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Atkinson, Jourdan, draft, proofs, and correspondence, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - BA, Bacon, Edmund, draft, 1973 Baffoun, Alya, draft, undated Bali, R.S., draft, 1973 Ballonof, Paul A. conference paper, 1973 Banerjee, A.R., conference paper, 1973 Bank, David J., draft, 1974 Baran, Jitka S.L, conference paper, 1973 Barnlund, Dean C., conference paper, 1973 Bansal, I.J.S., conference paper, 1973 Barwicke, Laura J. draft, 1973 Baskakov, N.A., conference paper, 1973 Bassing, Allen, conference paper, 1973 Basu, Amitabha, conference paper, 1973 Bernardi, B., reprint, undated Bharati, M. reprint, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - BE, Bean, Susan S., conference paper, 1973 Beckford, George L., conference paper, 1973 Bedaux, R.M.A., conference paper, 1973 Belin-Millerson, J. conference paper, 1973 Ben-Ami, Issachar, conference paper and draft, 1973 Benoist, Jean, conference paper, 1973 Benoit, Emile, draft, 1973 Ben-Salem, Idlia, conference paper and French translation, 1973 Bernier, Ronald M., conference paper, 1973 Berthoud, Gerald, conference paper, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - BH-BO, Bhanu, V. Vijaya, conference paper, 1973 Bianco, Caro, conference paper, 1973 Bishop, Charles A., conference papers, 1973 Borgenhammar, Edgar, draft, 1973 Bosse, William R. drat, 1973 Bouloux, C., G. Jaeger and Y. Marty, conference paper, 1973 Breton, Yvan, conference paper, 1973 Bringeus, Nils-Arvid, conference paper, 1973 Brink, Pamela, J., conference paper, 1973 Brook. S.I., conference paper, 1973 Brown, Margaret Kimball, conference paper, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - BU, Buchdahl, David, conference paper, 1973 Bunak, V.V., conference paper, 1973 Butzer, Karl W., conference paper, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Battesti, T., drafts, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Berg, K.W., drafts, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Bharti, A, correspondence, draft, conference paper, reprint, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Billingham, B.W. and Barry I. Isaac, conference paper, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Bonet, Ofelia Macado, conference paper, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Bredahl-Peterson, F.E., 1973 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Bowman, David L., Introductions for editions, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Buechler, J.M.H., paper for publication, 1973-1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Busygin, E.P. and N.V. Zorin, conference paper, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - CA-CH, Camejo, Acton, conference paper, 1973 Cantacuzino, Georges, conference paper, 1973 Capitanio, Mariantonia, conference paper, 1973 De Carmargo e Almeida, F., and Lourdes Rego Novaes, conference paper, 1973 Cartwright, R.A., conference paper, 1973 De Carvalho-Neto, Paulo, conference paper with translation, 1973 Casey, Albert E., cornellia Holland, Worth W. Barham, J.G. Casey, Barbar Long, and Eleanor L. Downey, abstract, 1973 Castell, Richard W. conference paper, 1973 Cattarinussi, Bernardo, conference paper, 1973 Chakravartti, M. R., abstract, 1973 Chamla, M.C., conference paper, 1973 Chao, Paul, conference paper, 1973 Chatterjee, B.K. and G.D. Kumar, conference paper, 1973 Chaudhuri, Buddhadeb, conference paper, 1973 Chesnow, Ai.V., conference paper, 1973 Chevrette, Louis, conference paper, 1973 Chevannes, Barry, conference paper, 1973 Chiao, Chien, conference paper, 1973 Chikovani, M.J., conference paper, 1973 Chipp, Sylvia A., conference paper, 1973 Chlenov, M.A., conference paper, 1973 Chritianssona Noel D. Broadbent, conference paper, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - CI-CL, Ciaovârnache, Marta and M. Bâlan, M., conference paper, 1973 Clark, Woodrow W., conference paper, 1973 Cloak Jr., F.T., conference paper, 1973 Closs, Alois, conference paper with translation, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - CO-CU, Cochran, Gylnn, conference paper, 1973 Cohn, Michael, conference paper, 1973 Comhaire, Jean L., conference paper, 1973 Comşa, Eugen, conference papers and translations, 1973 Constans, J., conference papers, 1973 Cordun, Val, conference paper, 1973 Correnti, V, M. Cresta, G.B. Panatta, E. Capucci, F. Vecchi. G. Spedini, Cordun, Val, conference papers, 1973 Cortazar, A.R., Cordun, Val, conference paper, 1973 Cove, John J. draft, undated Crognier, Emile, conference paper, 1973 Cubelic, Tvrtko, conference paper, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Cardich, Augusto (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Chaudhuri, Dulal, draft, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Chlenov, M. A., conference paper, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Choldin, Harvey M., draft, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Conrad, R. and W. Dye, draft, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Corrain, Cleto, draft, 1972 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Cooper, Kenneth, draft, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Corning, P.A. and C.H., draft, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - DA-DE, Danda, Ajit K., conference paper, 1973 Darnell, Regna, conference paper, 1973 Danilovea, E.I. and L.I. Timoshinko, conference paper, 1973 Davide, D.T. and R.R. Grilletto, conference paper and translation, 1973 Deblock, R. and R. Fenart, conference paper, 1973 Décsy, Gyula, conference paper, 1973 Dégh, Linda, and Andrew Vázsonyi, draft, 1973 Dej, A.I., conference paper, 1973 Delange-Fry, Jacquelin, draft, undated Derrett, J. Duncan, conference paper, 1973 Deva, Indra, draft, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 15)